When I was going through my wardrobe
我收拾衣柜的时候
I found an extra hairpin on the floor
在地板上我发现了一个多余的发夹
That's nothing, I found her hair in my bed.
那不算什么，我还在床上发现了她的头发
Just another tragedy of a down-and-out, I guess
我想，那只是另一出心力交瘁的悲剧，
For I'm selling the thing
我所卖出的东西
That means every thing to my life...
代表了我的生命和我的幸福的一切...
Some women bring happines...
有的女人，她们走到哪儿，欢乐就跟到哪儿；
wherever they go.Others, whenever they go.
有些，则是及时行乐
I do both.
我二者兼顾
Husbands like tosee me come...
丈夫们乐意看到我来，
wives prefer to seeme go.
妻子们则喜欢送我走
There she is.That's her.
她在那，那就是她
Whose husband didn't she sleep with?
她谁的丈夫没睡过啊?
- Who's she with now?- Who knows.
- 她现在跟谁在一起啊?- 谁知道
- She's older than I thought.- Look. Watch.
- 她比我想的老- 看，看好
This will teach her.
这会给她个教训
I'm sorry, Mrs Erlynne, but that account was closed.
对不起，Erlynne太太,但是那个账户已经
By Mrs Fairchild.
被Fairchild太太停了
I wish you'd told me before I ordered the Bordeaux.
我希望你在我点Bordeaux酒之前告诉我就好了
What Bordeaux, Mrs Erlynne?
什么Bordeaux酒, Erlynne太太?
Joe, you're my kind of guy.
Joe, 你是我喜欢的那类男人
- Is she behind me?- In the blue.
- 她在我后面吗?- 穿兰色衣服
Charge it to Senator Kleghorn.
那就算在Kleghorn参议员的帐上吧
That's Mrs Kleghorn sitting next to Mrs Fairchild.
Fairchild太太边上坐的就是Kleghorn太太
- What a small world.- And Mrs Winters on her right.
- 世界可真小啊- 她左边的是Winters太太
And getting smaller.
哦，越来越小了
You wanna go outthe back?
你要从后面走吗?
No, if you go out the back, you'll never come in the front, Joe.
不，如果你从后门走就再也别想从前面进来了，Joe
A lady always leaves the way she came.
淑女怎么来，便怎么走
I thought my husband had more taste.
你看看她，我以为我丈夫更有品呢
So sorry to hear you're leaving us, Mrs Erlynne.
听说你要走真难过，Erlynne太太
- I'm leaving you?- I'll prepare your bill.
我要退房？- 我给您备好账单
I ask you to make me an offer
我让你开个价，
I don't know how much it will bring
我不知道那会值多少
It isn't a lot...
虽然那并不算太多
but it's all I've got
但那已经倾我所有
Pooled by an old gold ring?
把老金戒也一起卖了？
It's known me as poor as a beggar
有时我一贫如洗，象个乞丐
And it's known me as rich as a king
有时我挥金如土，象个国王
And it's known me in hell And in heaven as well
我既下过地狱，又上过天堂
Pooled by an old gold ring?
把老金戒也一起卖了？
My sudden changeing circumstance...
我环境的突变...
was not the only reason for my departure.
并不是我离开的唯一理由
The italian coast in summerattracts the rich and famous.
夏季的意大利海滩吸引着富者和名人
I'm infamous and poor.
我没名气又穷
Close enough.
挺接近的
One door closes,another opens.
一扇门关闭，另一扇开启了
Sometimes that door isnot the one you expect.
有时那并不是你所期待的门
I saw my chance anddecided to take it.
我看到了我的机会并决定抓住
Meg, dear. Come along.Come along.
Meg, 亲爱的，快过来
Ah, Giuseppina.
啊, Giuseppina
She's my friend.Give her a discount.
她是我的朋友，给她一个折扣
Come here.
过来
It's the best glove shop in the city.
这是城里最好的手套店
She'll give you a good discount.
她会给你个好折扣
You go along, I'll find yourhusband, don't worry.
你去吧，我会找到你丈夫的，别担心
This way, madam.
这边请，女士
These are pretty.
这真漂亮
- Your hand looks about right.- I beg your pardon?
- 你的手看上去差不多- 你说什么?
My little sister. She wasadamant about every detail but...
我的小妹妹，她把细节都说了...
neglected to tell me the size.Would you mind?
就是忘了告诉我尺码，你介意吗?
Oh, no, of course not.
不，当然不会
It's always a little snugthe first time.
第一次有点挤
Maybe you should takeoff your ring.
也许你该退去戒指
It's my wedding ring,I never take it off.
那是我的结婚戒指，我不能把它拿下来
The other hand, then.
那，就另一只手吧
No need to button it. You can seeit fits perfectly.
不要系扣，你能看出来很合手的
Lord Darlington,you depraved man.
Darlington大人，你这个堕落的人
What have you been up to?
你打算干什么啊?
Ignore him, Meg, dear.He's a great sinner.
别理他, Meg, 亲爱的他可是个大罪人
But an excellent bridge partner.
可却是个了不起的桥梁合伙人
Or I would never tolerate him.
要不我肯定会忍受不了他的
- Do you know each other?- The year I spent in the London office.
- 你们彼此认识了吗?- 在伦敦办事处的那年认识的
I told you about John.But you've met.
我跟你提过John但，你们已经认识了吧
- No. It's nice to meet you.- It's a pleasure, Mrs Windemere.
- 没有，认识你很荣幸- 很荣幸，Windemere太太
Your wife was helping me selectgloves for my mother.
你太太正帮我给我母亲选手套
- Your sister, you said.- Either one.
- 你妹妹，你说的- 两个人的
We should have dinner.Where are you staying?
我们该一起用餐你们住哪?
The Grand, but we're tryingto find a villa.
住Grand,但我们正在找别墅
So late in the season.I warned you.
在这个季节有点晚了，我警告过你的
I know one that's available.
我知道一个合适的
Isn't it an election year inthe wild west?
今年是狂野西部的竞选年吧?
Who says I'm running?
谁说我参选了?
- It's perfect. It's beaultiful.- Did I mention the ghost?
- 真完美，太美了- 我提到鬼魂了吗?
I feel like a princessin a fairly tale.
我能想到的都在这了我觉得自己象童话中的公主
You are a princess.
你就是公主
That's because Imarried the prince.
那是因为我嫁给了王子
I have her completely fooled,poor girl.
我把她完全骗住了，可怜的女孩
If I could fool a woman aspretty, I wouldn't be a bachelor.
如果我能骗到一个象你太太一样漂亮的女孩我就不会仍是单身汉了
- Now you've made her blush.- Don't be silly.
- 看你让她不好意思了- 别傻了
Come and see the paintings.
来看看画吧
Come on.
走
Good evening.
晚上好
Lady Plymdale?
Plymdale女士？
Oh, is she the onewith the big...
哦，她就是那个有大...
Feet. Enourmous feet.Poor old Plymdale.
脚，著名的大脚可怜的老Plymdale
- Ace, Queen, King, Jack.- No honours.
- A, Q, K ，J- 真没面子
No, no, John's yacht,John's rules.
不，John的游艇John的规矩
- Have it.- Thank you.
- 拿去- 谢谢你
Huge feet. Pontoons.
大脚，浮桥
If desire had an antidote, it wouldbe those pontoons of hers.
如果期待能够修正，那就是她的浮桥了
I grow ill thinking of then.
我想的都得病了
How many times have youbeen divorced, Tuppy?
你离过多少次婚了, Tuppy?
- Three, four? I've simply lost count.- That's bigamy.
- 三次，四次? 我不会数了- 那是重婚
Bigamy is having one wifetoo many.
重婚是有过多妻子
So is monogamy
那是一夫一妻
One should always have a properbasis for marriage. A mutual...
每个人都该有个合理的婚姻基础一个相互……
- Misunderstanding?- Exactly.
- 误解?- 没错
A man can't be happywith one woman.
男人只有一个女人是不会快乐的
A man can be happy with any woman.As long as he doesn't love her.
只要不爱，男人跟任何女人都会快乐
For a man who's never thoughtof getting married...
对于一个永不言婚的男人来说...
you seem to know an awfullot about it.
你知道的够多的
I've thought very seriously of marrying.That's why I'm still single.
我对婚姻考虑甚为周详所以至今未婚
Hear, hear.
听到了
I just haven't met the right woman.Look at Cecil, still with Edna.
我只是还没遇到合适的看Cecil, 还跟Edna在一起
One keeps one's eyes wide openbefore the wedding...
一个人该在婚礼前大睁双眼...
and half shut after.
其后就要睁一眼闭一眼了
- That's all there is to it.- Exactly.
- 就那么回事- 没错
I fancy raising the stakes.
我想结束了
Oh, lucky blighter!
哦，幸运的家伙
You don't look as ifyou're enjoying yourself.
你看着不怎么开心啊
Oh, I am. It's a verynice party.
哦，我开心，晚会很好
- Can I get you a drink?- No, thank you. I don't drink.
- 我能给你拿个饮品么?- 不了，谢谢，我不喝
You don't drink?
你不喝?
- Do I seem like a prig?- No, of course not.
- 我看上去象个假正经的人吗?- 不，当然不是
- It's the way I was raised.- In a convent?
- 我就是那样被带大的- 在修道院吗?
By my Aunt Julia.My father's sister.
是我的Julia姑姑我父亲的姐姐
My mother died when Iwas very little.
我幼年丧母
It's the only picture Ihave of her.
这是我有的她唯一的照片
My father never remarried.
我父亲从没再婚
She's every bit as beaultifulas her daughter.
她似她女儿般美貌
Have I offended you?I meant it as a compliment.
我冒犯你了吗?我是在恭维你呢
- You pay me too many compliments.- I'll stop at once.
- 你过于恭维我了- 我会马上停止
- Thank you.- Just so you know, I meant every one.
- 谢谢你- 你只要知道，我是真心的
You pretend to be bad, but...
你假装坏，但...
- you're not really.- There is no good or bad.
- 其实你不是- 没有好坏之分
People are either charmingor tedious.
人只有迷人和沉闷之分
If I've been the latter,I sincerely apologize.
如果我是后者，我真诚道歉
- I'd like us to become friends.- We already are, aren't we?
- 我希望我们能成朋友- 我们已经是了，对吧?
Not if you keep flattering me andpaying me silly compliments.
那就别奉承我或是说些愚蠢的恭维话
Define silly.
定义“愚蠢”
I want your word.
你得保证
I find the best way to keep myword is never to give it.
我发现要想不食言就别乱保证
It's always a pleasureto see a pretty woman.
看到漂亮女人永远都是一种荣幸
Good day.
天气不错
It has to be somethingreally special...
一定得是特别的东西...
My wife's birthday.
是我妻子的生日
This is a very specialobject.
这个非常特别
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样?
The sapphire matches your eyes.
蓝宝石很衬你的眼睛
It's for my wife.
是给我妻子的
A man should never buy hiswife jewellery.
男人可不该给妻子买珠宝
And why is that?
那是为什么?
It makes her wonder whathe bought his mistress.
那会让她猜测他会给情妇买什么
My wife has nothing towonder about.
我妻子没什么可猜测的
She's a lucky woman.
她是个幸运的女人
If I was your wife...
如果我是你妻子...
- this is what I'd want.- A fan?
- 这才是我想要的- 一把扇子?
Not for stirring the air,for stirring the heart.
不为鼓动空气，为了鼓动心灵
For centuries...
是经历百年...
an erotic language betweenmen an women.
男女间的性欲语言
If a woman placed it on her breastlike this, it meant "I love you".
如果女人把它这样放在胸前那意思是“我爱你”
"When can I see you?"
"我几时能见你?"
"Wait for me."
"等我"
"You may kiss me."
"你可以亲吻我"
"We're being watched."
"我们正被监视"
I'm sold.
我被出卖了
How much?
多少钱?
No, it's not for sale.
不，那个不是卖品
Not for sale.
非卖品？
It would break mymom's heart.
那会伤透我妈妈的心
My mama.
我妈妈
Real gold.
真金的
If you give him everything, who'sgoing to buy me an espresso?
如果你倾囊而出谁给我买浓缩咖啡啊?
My back.
我的后背啊
And Americans everywhere.
而且到处都是美国人
You'd never know there was adepression in that country.
你根本不会知道他们国家正经历经济危机
Please, something to drinkbefore I faint.
拜托，我晕倒前喝点东西吧
They don't shop, they pillage.
他们不是买东西，他们在掠夺
And they speak loudly.
而且他们说话声音太吵
Could the entire nation behard of hearing?
难道他们整个民族都有听力障碍吗?
Something in the diet, perhaps?
可能是吃的东西有问题，也许?
But we have Americanfriends, mama.
但是我们有美国朋友啊，妈妈
They don't need to know whatwe say about them.
但他们不需要知道我们是怎么讲究他们的
If everyone knew what everyonesaid of each other...
如果每个人都知道别人背后怎么讲究自己...
there wouldn't be four friendsin the world.
那人生在世不会有超过四个朋友了
I like America.
我喜欢美国
Name me another society that's gonefrom barbarism to decadence...
你找不到一个社会由荒蛮进入颓废
without bothering to create acivilization in between.
都不劳神经历文明时代
Tribute to American efficiency.
全拜美国人所赐
- There's Mr Windemere.- He must join us then.
- Windemere先生在那- 他得加入我们
He can't see you, mama.
他看不见你，妈妈
Who's that with him?
跟他一起的是谁?
Looks like his wife.
好像是他妻子
No, I don't think it is.
不，我看不是
I can't see now.They're getting into the car.
我现在看不见了，他们进车里了
It must be the wife if she'sgetting into the car.
如果她进车里肯定是他妻子
It wasn't her.
不是的
Then I must know who it is.
那我就得知道到底是谁
I think we should mind ourown business.
我觉得我们该管自己的事
My own business bores me.
我自己的事太无聊了
I much prefer other people's.
我更喜欢管别人闲事
Poor little Meg,she's so sweet.
可怜的Meg，她多可爱
And the girl has no mother.
而且她没妈妈
- I want to take her to my breast.- I had a similar thought.
- 我想把她揽在怀里- 我曾有过类似想法
I don't suppose Mr Windemerewould be pleased to hear it.
我猜Windemere先生不会想听到这些
Merital bliss...
神圣的赐福...
is a great burden to placeon two people, Tuppy.
对两个人是巨大的负担, Tuppy
Sometimes a third person isneeded to lighten the load.
有时第三者是摆脱负担的必需
It would seem,Mr Windemere agrees with you.
看起来， Windemere先生是赞许你的
I can guess what you were doing.
我能猜出你干了什么
Shopping for my birthday present?
给我买生日礼物?
I was right.
我对了
What did you get?
你买什么了?
Not a thing. You're too oldfor presents.
什么也没买，你老得不配买礼物
- A hint. A tiny speck of a hint.- You'll have to wait and see.
- 一个提示，一个小不点的提示- 你得等着瞧
- Perfume?- No, stop it.
- 香水?- 不，别猜了
A book of poems?
一本诗集?
A dress?
一件套装?
A crocodile handbag like theone the Contessa has...
一个象女爵爷提的，用小爪子做扣的
with the little claws hangingoff the bottom?
鳄鱼皮的手袋？
No more guessing.
别猜了
Robert?
Promise we won't end up like thoseold married couples...
保证我，我们不会落得跟那些老家伙一样的下场...
sitting opposite each other atdinner with nothing to say.
虽然在吃饭时面对面坐着但无话可谈
You, with nothing to say?
你，无话可谈?
I promise.
我保证
We'll always tell eachother the truth?
我们要一直彼此讲真话?
Except around birthdays.
除了生日
You're feisty.What have you been reading?
你很活跃啊在看什么书?
- What do you mean?- No, it's nice.
- 什么意思?- 没有，挺好
Turn out the lights.
关上灯
- But I like to see you.- Please?
-可我想看你－拜托
I'll take them all.
我都要了
- Good day, madam.- Excuse me.
- 你好，女士- 请原谅
I bought a suit.
我买了一件套装
It's being altered.For Margaret Windemere.
正在改，给Margaret Windemere
Ah, Mrs Windemere.One moment, please.
啊, Windemere太太请稍等
Thank you.
谢谢
Forgive me.You're American, aren't you?
请原谅你是美国人，对吧？
I'm from New York.Mrs Erlynne.
我从New York来，Erlynne太太
Rhode Island.Mrs Windemere.
Rhode 岛，Windemere太太
I need an opinion from here.Now be honesty.
我需要点建议，真心话
Would you wear it?
你会穿它吗?
Well, it doesn't leave muchto the imagination, does it?
这会让人失去想像力，是吧?
That depends on the imagination.Some men have more than others.
那要看有多少想像力，有些男人比其他的多些
I suppose it's certainly immodest.
我觉得肯定不够端庄
Do you think it's vulgar?
你觉得它粗俗吗?
Some people might.
有些人会那么想
Is your husband with you?I'd love a man's opinion.
你丈夫跟你一起来了吗?我需要一个男人的意见
I can tell you.He's very conservative.
我可以告诉你，他很保守
A woman doesn't knowher own husband.
一个女人是不会了解她丈夫的
Oh, I know Robert.We've been married over a year.
哦，我了解 Robert我们都结婚快一年了
A year? Pratically forever.
一年？简直就跟一辈子似的
Here it is, signora.
给你，女士
Oh, thank you.
哦 谢谢
Thank you very much.Come back again to see us.
多谢你，请再光顾
- Goodbye- You're not taking the hat?
- 再见- 你不要帽子吗?
The colour looks perfect on you.Don't you like it?
颜色很合你，你不要吗?
No, I've nowhere to wear it.It's not exactly church on sunday.
不，我没场合戴，周日并不上教堂
Why not?
为什么?
Can you imagine whatpeople would say?
你能想像人们会怎么说吗?
Well, if we're always guided byother people's thoughts...
哦，如果我们总让别人左右我们...
what's the point ofhaving our own?
那还要自己的头脑干什么用呢?
It was nice meeting you,Mrs Ewin.
高兴人士你，Ewin太太
- Erlynne.- Erlynne.
- Erlynne- Erlynne
She was staying in a pensione...
她本来在一个小旅馆...
now she's in a villa afew minutes from the club.
现在她住在离俱乐部几分钟远的别墅里
He's there.
他在那
I can't help seeing him.
我老是看见他
He comes and goes allhours of the day.
他整天来来去去
Of course, in public, she'salways with other men.
当然，在公开场合她总是跟其他男人在一起
She wears nothing butthe latest fashions.
她只穿最新的时装
Somebody must be giving her a verygenerous allowance.
肯定有某人给她很慷慨的资助
Silence!
安静
And she'll have her hand in Tuppy'spocket next, if he doesn't wake up.
如果Tuppy还不清醒过来她就快把手伸进他口袋里了
She's nothing better thana common prostitute.
她不过是个公众的妓女
And Mrs Windemere has no idea?
Windemere太太不知道吗?
None at all.
根本不知道
- I'm sorry.- She must be on the terrace.
- 对不起- 她肯定在露台
I'm sorry, I didn'tmean to frighten you.
对不起，我可不想吓到你
- Yes, you did.- Yes, you did. What's that?
- 可你吓到我了- 没错，那是什么?
I'm making a menu formy birthday party.
我正准备我生日晚会的菜单
What's italian for lobster?
龙虾的意大利文怎么说?
Aragosta.
Aragosta
Very good. Now you've made me hungry.
很好，现在你把我搞的饿起来了
Leave it, come on. Everyone'slunching at the club.
放下吧，我们走所有人都在俱乐部吃饭
Okay. I'll get Robert.
好，我叫上Robert
I thought you agreed not tocall me at home?
我以为你同意不往我家打电话?
How can I seduce you if youalways bring your husband?
你老带着丈夫，我怎么引诱你啊?
Too slow. Come on.
太慢了，走吧
All right.
好吧
Yes, I'll be there.In an hour.
好，我会在一小时到
Okay, in an hour.
好，一小时
It's quitting time.We're going to lunch.
该休息了，我们要去吃饭
Can't, sorry.
不行，对不起
- You're working?- Money never sleeps.
- 你在工作吗?- 钱可不睡觉
Bugger!
该死
All paying jobs absorb...
付钱的工作吸引人
and degrade the mind.
也会使人堕落
You never had a paying job.
你没有付钱的工作
I rest my case.
我在休庭阶段
Cultivated leisure isman's true calling.
有教养的休闲才是男人的去处
- I have to send some telegrams in town.- I'll wait for you.
- 我要进城发电报- 我要等你
I'll be all afternoon.I don't want you to waste the day.
我要一下午，我可不想浪费你一天（支票：给Erlynne太太，400元）
- Do you mind, John?- Do I mind?
- 你介意吗, John?- 我介意?
No, of course not.
不，当然不会
If you have to escort that woman tothe opera, please don't sit with us.
如果你非要护送那女人去看歌剧别跟我们坐一起
Think of Alessandra.
想想Alessandra
Mrs Erlynne has her own seats.
Erlynne 太太有自己的座位
Who pays for them?
谁付的钱?
Her uncle just died.She's come into some money.
她叔叔刚死，有些进项
And Mr Windemere's visits?
Windemere先生的拜访呢?
He's managing her investments,of course.
他当然是在运作她的投资了
You're so fond of gossip.
你太爱嚼舌根了
You don't give the truth a chanceto put its pants on.
根本没给真相一个穿裤子的机会
It's not the truth that's going withoutpants, dear Tuppy.
亲爱的Tuppy，没穿裤子的不是真相
Would you mind not smoking?
你介意别抽烟吗?
Opera makes me feel so romantic.
歌剧让我感觉太浪漫了
Anything too stupid to besaid is sung.
歌唱真是无聊之极
How's that romantic?
有什么浪漫的?
And the women arealways so fleshy!
而且女人也都太肉感了
Excuse me, that's my foot.
对不起，那是我的脚
Right over here?
就在那吗?
What did I tell you?
我怎么跟你说的？
Stop, boy!
别那样，孩子
Fried anchovies and clamsin a bog. Delicious.
沼泽里的炸凤尾鱼配蛤喇美味
Careful, it's hot.
小心，很烫
You told Robert we weregoing to the club.
你跟Robert说我们去俱乐部
I have a very poor senseof direction.
我方向感极差
You have a very poor senseof decorum.
你的礼貌才差
I never use that word.I'm not sure what it means.
我从不用那个字，把握不好意思
- At the club we'd be with other people.- You're right.
- 在俱乐部就得跟其他人在一起- 说对了
Here we are,in the sunshine...
而我们在这里，在阳光里...
eating fish, literallyjust off the boat...
吃着刚从船上打来的鱼...
when we could be squashed between LordTubby and Cecil the Scintillating...
代替了在Tubby大人和光彩照人的 Cecil中间挤着……
listening to one or theother gripe about his digestion...
听他们抱怨自己的消化病
while the Contessa, in acounter-medley, wails that...
同时混杂着女爵爷哀号……
Alessandra cares more for...
Alessandra比关心自己...
the mating habits of theblue bellied finch...
还更关心蓝腹鸟交配习惯...
than those of her own species,and the widow Plymdale...
Plymdale寡妇转着怪异的眼睛...
bats her eyes logingly everypassing pair of trou.
死盯着别人的裤子
All of which is time wellspent in my book.
那是我看书时打发的时光
So, yes, I take your point.
所以，是的，我接受你的意见
I can't argue. At the club, we'dbe with other people.
我无法争辩，在俱乐部我们得跟其他人一起
Afraid we'll be seen?
害怕我们被发现吗?
Set the chins wagging?
给人嚼舌根?
Do you know what I findworse than being talked about?
你知道我发现比被人嚼舌根更可怕的是什么?
Not being talked about at all.
根本不被人谈起
Mrs Erlynne will see you upstairs.
Erlynne太太在楼上见你
In her bedroom.
在她卧室
Thank you. I won't be long.
谢谢，我不会久呆
"I won't be long."
"我不会久呆"
This is expensive.
这很贵
- Nothing but the best for you.- I know, I paid for it.
- 只给你最好的- 我知道，是我付的钱
Well, there is that.
都在那了
Should we be drinking thisearly in the day?
我们该这么早就喝酒吗?
Well, somewhere in the worldit's very late.
世界上的某地现在很晚了
I don't want you thinkingI make a habit of this.
我不想让你觉得这样成习惯了
Is that why you look so guilty?
那是你看上去内疚的原因吗?
I don't like lying to her.
我不喜欢跟她说谎
I should go.She's only gone to lunch.
我得走了，她只是去吃饭
This is all the cashI have right now.
这是我现在所有的现金
I'll set you up with an account.
我会给你建个账号
You can draw on it directly.
你就可以直接提取了
I met Meg.
我遇到Meg了
It was by chance.
是个巧遇
It's all right,she had no idea who I was.
没事的，她不知道我是谁
You spoke to her?
你跟她说话了吗?
Yes, for a minute.She's very pretty.
对，很短，她很漂亮
How did you two meet?Was it love at first sight?
你们俩怎么遇上的?是一见钟情吗?
I have to go.
我得走了
I'm curious. It's only natural.
我好奇，很自然的
There's no pointto these questions.
这些问题没意义
- Do you love her?- Very much.
- 你爱她吗?- 很爱
I'd rather cut off my armthan see Meg hurt.
我宁可断臂也不想让Meg受伤
Are you protecting her oryour reputation?
你是在保护她还是保护你的名声?
You don't know me at all.
你对我一无所知
Did he work on yourwedding night?
他在你们的新婚之夜也工作吗?
He's very conscientiousand I respect him for it.
他很尽责，我为此而敬重他
Suppose it wasn't work,suppose he had a mistress.
假设不是因为工作，假设他有情妇
Well, I couldn't respect that.
哦，那我可不敬重了
Once a wife's been betrayed...
一旦妻子遭背叛...
she has the freedom todo likewise.
她就有依样做的理由
No, that would make her as badas her husband, wouldn't it?
不，那岂不让她跟那丈夫一样坏了吗?
Modern marriage thrives onmutual deception.
现代婚姻因彼此欺骗而兴旺
We are completely honestwith each other.
我们彼此完全忠诚
You should makehim your model.
你该以他为榜样
I intend to.From this moment on.
我正打算，从现在开始
Don't you like it?
你不喜欢吗?
Oh, I'm saving it for Robert.He loves figs.
哦，我给Robert留着，他喜欢无花果
Share mine, then.
那吃我的吧
Can we go to thetelegraph office?
我们能去电报局吗?
He probably hasn't eaten.
他可能还没吃东西呢
Alberto? Fabrizio?
Oh, what's his name?
哦，他叫什么?
Mario?
Barman.
酒保
Whisky.
威士忌
And another thing, your Mrs Erlynnehas no principles at all.
另外, 你的Erlynne太太完全没有原则
I like people more than principles.
我喜欢人甚于原则
And people without principles,even better.
没原则的人就更好了
But Lord Augustus, she onlywants you for your money.
但是Augustus大人她只是要你的钱啊
Now why shouldn't she?It's my best asset.
她干嘛不能？那是我最好的资产
Old-ish, fat-ish,absolutely no brain...
又老又胖，完全无脑
heaps and heaps of banknotes.
成堆的钞票
No need toput yourself down, Tuppy.
并不需要贬低自己，Tuppy
Your friends can always do that.
让你的朋友们来嘛
Down by the marina, strolling along,pretty as you please...
在码头，一起徘徊，跟你一样美……
guess who I saw withLord Darlington?
猜我看见谁跟Darlington大人在一起?
They haven't seen him today.
他们今天没看见他
Do you know wheremy husband is?
你知道我丈夫在哪吗?
I thought he leftafter you, signora.
我以为他跟你一起走了，女士
Robert?
How was lunch?
午饭怎样?
We went to the telegraph office.Where were you?
我们去电报局了，你去哪了?
Well, we must have justmissed each other.
我们也许刚巧错过了
Now I see uncle.He's with the american woman.
现在我看见叔叔了他跟那美国女人在一起
Too much rouge and notenough clothing.
口红过多，衣服过少
She's appealing to the worstin the poor man.
她使尽招数引诱那可怜的男人
It's what women do best.
那是女人的拿手好戏
I heard she left New Yorkwithout paying her hotel bill.
我听说她离开New York连酒店的帐都没付
Quite a scandal.
真是个丑闻
- Who? Someone you know?- Someone you don't want to know.
- 谁? 你认识的人吗?- 是个你不想认识的人
No. Steer clear.
不，Steer Clear
She's the onewith Lord Augustus.
她就是跟Augustus大人在一起的
You've met Mrs Erlynne,haven't you?
你已经认识Erlynne太太了，是吧？
- No.- But I've seen you.
- 没有.- 可我看见你了
Oh, was that your foot?
哦，那是你的脚吗?
Wherever do you findshoes to fit?
你到哪去找合脚的鞋啊?
My feet are in perfect proportionto the rest of me.
我的脚跟我身体其他部分很成比例
Oh, yes, of course.
哦，是的，当然
Though they have a habit of findingthemselves in peculiar places.
尽管他们有在奇特的地方出现的习惯
Those people arestaring right at us.
那些人在盯着我们看呢
Who?
谁?
Don't worry about them.
别理会他们
It's my brother's wife andher friend, Lady Plymdale.
那是我哥哥的妻子和她的朋友Plymdale女士
Lord Plymdale passed onlast year. Liver, I think.
Plymdale大人去年死了，肝，我想
- Poor woman.- Oh, yes, very sad.
- 可怜的女人- 哦，是的，很悲惨
Her hair turned quitegold with grief.
因为伤心，她的头发越发的金色了
Erlynne, that's right.She came into some money.
Erlynne, 对了，她有了一些进项
- I made an investment for her.- An inheritance, I suppose?
- 我为她管理投资- 是遗产吧，我猜?
The woman in the shop.I told you, remember?
商店里的女人，我告诉过你的，记得吗?
The dress?
套装?
No, back and almost no front.You could see everything.
不，后背，几乎没有前片你什么都能看见
It was indecent.
很不像样
You're just not used toItalian fashions, that's all.
你只是不习惯意大利时装而已
No, I'm sure your wife ison the mark.
我觉得你妻子挺合拍的
Mrs Erlynne is anotorious Jezebel.
Erlynne太太是个声名狼藉的无耻女人
That's a slanderous statement. If youcan't back it up, I wouldn't repeat it.
那是诽谤，如果你不收回，我不会重复
Robert always gives everybodythe benefit of the doubt.
Robert总是给不随便评价他人的
I'm sorry, I just don't like gossip.
对不起，我只是不喜欢流言
Gossip's all right, it's themoralising that's in poor taste.
流言没什么，这是口味低下的布道
She's got her eye on me,if you know what I mean.
她看上我了，你该懂我意思
So I wouldn't worry about what theysay, it's all cats in a bag.
所以我根本不担心他们说什么不过是囊中之物吧了
Why, what do they say about me?
怎么了，他们怎么说我的？
That I'm a wanton woman?
说我是荡妇?
Brazen - with a past.
厚颜无耻，背景复杂
A brazen woman.Oh, dear.
一个厚颜无耻的女人，哦，我的天啊
You're very brazen yourselfto be seen in my company.
由我陪伴的你才真是厚颜无耻呢
I've got a bit of a pastmyself you know.
我也有个复杂的背景啊
Married and divorced twice.
结婚离婚了两次
Every experience is of value andwhatever you say...
每个经历都有价值
about marriage it certainlyis an experience.
无论你怎么讲究婚姻都肯定是有价值的
People call somethingan experience...
当人们讲究经历的时候...
They usually meanit was a mistake.
他们多半说的是错误
I couldn't agree more.
我无任同意
We've all got a couple ofskeletons in the closet.
我们都在储藏间里藏着几具骷髅
If they're going to rattle,they may as well dance.
如果他们要喋喋不休还不如干脆跳舞
You're absolutely right.
你完全正确
Whenever anyone agrees with me,I'm sure I must be wrong.
只要有人赞同我我一定错了
You like to be theodd man out, do you?
你喜欢作最后一个剩下的人，是吧?
I'll never understand women.
我从来就不能理解女人
Women don't want to be understood,they want to be loved.
女人不需要人理解，只需要人爱
You're dead wrong on that.
你这就大错了
You're very understanding.
你真善解人意
That girl in lilac,do you know her?
戴丁香花的女人，你认识吗?
Oh, yes, it's Robert's wife.
哦，是的，那是Robert的妻子
All lovey-dovey,very charming.
很可爱，很迷人
I wish she'd stop staring at me.
我希望她别再盯着我了
She isn't at all.
她没有
Those women must begiving her an earful.
那些女人肯定在给她进言呢
- You mustn't mind.- I don't, as a rule.
- 你别介意- 按照惯例，我没有
Look, it's terribly stuffy in here,I can hardly breathe.
你看，这很乏味，我都不能喘气了
Shall we go? Would you mind?
我们走吧，你介意吗？
I can't think of anythingI'd mind less.
我根本一点都不介意
Good.
好
I can't believe it - she's got him!
我不敢相信，她钓上他了
Poor Tuppy.
可怜的Tuppy
Shall I get a taxi?
我叫个出租车吧?
- Could we walk?- Why not.
- 可以走路吗?- 为何不呢
Beautiful city.
漂亮的城市
The Romans call it"The Land of the Sirens..."
罗马人叫它"妖妇之城"
from Homer's Odyssey.
出自荷马的《奥德赛》
Is that so? Aren't you clever?
真的吗?你真聪明
- I read it somewhere.- I like a good read myself.
- 我在哪里读到的- 我也喜欢阅读
Nothing too laborious. I don't wantto tamper with natural ignorance.
别太累，我不想影响自然的无知
- It's the key to happiness.- Do you really think so?
- 是快乐的钥匙- 你真那么想吗?
Absolutely. Good health,it's important, but...
绝对是，健康，很重要...
ignorance is the key. Too muchknowledge and you're doomed.
无知是钥匙，太多知识你就被限制住了
Well, here we are.
嗯，到了
Aren't you going to invite mein for a nightcap?
你都不邀请我进睡前酒吗?
The sirens were said to behalf woman, half monster.
传说中的妖妇是半人半魔
They lured the sailors withtheir songs.
她们用歌声引诱水手
The ships crashed on therocks and the men all drowned.
船只触礁，水手溺水
Oh, let's go in. You can tell memore about it.
哦，进去吧，你再多告诉我一些
Poor Lady Plymdale, I think shereally likes Tuppy.
可怜的Plymdale女士,我觉得她是真喜欢Tuppy
- Where do you suppose they went?- Who?
- 你觉得他们去哪里了?- 谁?
Tuppy and Mrs Erlynne.
Tuppy 和Erlynne太太
Probably back to her apartment.
可能回她住所了
Probably.
可能
Do you think he'll inviteher to my party?
你觉得他会邀请她参加我的舞会吗?
I'll make sure he doesn't.
我会确保他不能
- Well, don't be mean about it.- No, of course not.
- 别太刻薄了- 不，当然不会
It's just I don't want anyoneto be uncomfortable, you know?
只是我不想让任何人尴尬，明白吗?
Someone like that makesthings awkward.
那样的事会令局面很难受
You can say it's a small party.Private, just friends.
你就说是个小舞会，只是些朋友而已
- No investors.- All right.
- 没有投资人- 好
It's not just girl gossip. JohnDarlington knows all abou it.
那不只是女孩的流言，JohnDarlington 知道所有情况
He said her friend isa married man.
他说她的朋友是个已婚男人
It's disgusting.
真令人厌恶
You know what, people like tohear themselves talk.
你知道吗，人们喜欢听自己讲话
- Why do you insist on defending her?- I'm not defending her.
- 你干嘛要坚持为她辩护?- 我没替她辩护
Yes, you are.
你有
Let's drop it.
我们别说了
It's just... Should yoube helping her invest?
只是……你该替她管理投资吗?
Everyone knows how shecame into the money.
所有人都知道她钱的来路
New topic.
新话题
Close your eyes.
闭眼
- Robert?- Close your eyes.
- Robert?- 闭眼
It's after midnight.Happy birthday.
已经过午夜了生日快乐
- It's beautiful.- Do you like it?
- 真美- 你喜欢吗?
Thank you.
谢谢
- I love you.- I love you, too.
- 我爱你- 我也爱你
Oh, my!
哦，天啊
- Thank you.- Don't mention it.
- 谢谢- 别提了
You like it?
你喜欢吗?
Food is the rock...
食物是岩石...
on which we build.
由我们创造
No love is pure and simpleas the love of food.
没有爱象食物一样纯洁而简单
Love is rarely pure, Lord Augustus.And never simple.
爱少有纯洁，Augustus大人而且从不简单
I don't think you've beenin love, Mrs Erlynne.
我不认为你曾爱过，Erlynne太太
You may presumeto call me Stella...
你可以假称我Stella...
but don't presumeto know my heart.
但别假装你知道我的心
For your information,I'm always in love.
根据你的情报，我永远都在恋爱
Good. Excellent attitude.And you're beautiful.
好，出色的态度，而且你很美
Smart, too. Smarter than me,I expect, but...
也精明，比我精明，我希望……
that's not saying much,I'm afraid.
希望没说太多
No, I think I'll do very wellto marry you.
不，我觉得如果跟你结婚我会很好的
How very practical.
多实际啊
I've begun too many romancesout of sentiment.
我开始过太多不涉及情感的浪漫了
They always end in settlement.
最终都以结算为结局
I could listen to you all night,Lord Augustus.
我可以整夜听你倾诉Augustus大人
Tuppy, please.
请叫我Tuppy
You'll think about my offer?
你会考虑我的提议吗?
Men don't marry women like me.
男人不跟我这样的女人结婚的
There aren't any women like you.
那是因为没有你这样的女人
At least, not among the womenI've met, and I've met my share.
至少我认识的人里面没有我遇到可以分享的了
I was married - I didn't take to it.
我曾结婚，但不喜欢
People change. You mightfeel differently.
人会变，你会感受到不同的
When I think of it, I thinkof a room...
当我想到的时候我想到
where you can't open a window.
一个不能开窗的房间
Where there is no window.
因为没有窗户
Every day you wake upand the room is smaller.
每天醒来，你发现房间又变小了
You don't notice, not at first.It happens slowly.
你不会注意，开始不会逐渐发生
In inches.
一点点的
Then one morning,you open your eyes...
然后某天早晨你睁眼发现...
and the room is so small...
房间已经小的...
you can't move.
你无法腾挪了
You can't take a breath.
无法呼吸
You have to get out.
你不得不逃走
You can't think of anything else.
你什么事都无法想
Or anyone else.
什么人都无法想
You married the wrong man,that's all.
你只是嫁错了人
He married the wrong woman.
他娶错了人
It's late.
很晚了
It's time for bed.
该上床了
Sleep.
睡觉
"...Perchance to dream".
"偶然的梦境"
That's the bard, you know.I'm a bit of a reader myself.
是吟游诗人，你知道我自己也读过点书的
So you said. Goodnight, Tuppy.
照你说的，晚安，Tuppy
I hate the taste of tobacco.
我讨厌烟草味
Well - that's it then.
好，就这样
I quit. On the spot.
我戒了，当场
What else can I tell you?
我还能告诉你什么?
I'm a very rich man, you know.
我是个非常富有的人，你知道
You're a very nice man.
你是个非常好的人
Go to bed.
上床吧
You know, I'm glad I quit.
你知道，我很高兴戒烟了
Filthy habit, really.
肮脏的习惯，真的
Goodnight.
晚安
Is there going to be a lion tamer,or is it just the usual clowns?
是驯狮人或只是普通的小丑?
Robert was afraid it might rain.
Robert害怕会下雨呢
I just wanted a few people for dinnerbut he said you are only 21 once.
我本来只想几个人吃饭但他说你一生只得一次21岁
I know plenty of women who, of theirown accord, turn 35 year after year.
我认识很多女人，按照她们的记录年年都过35
I'm sure you can be 21 as many times.
我肯定你可以21岁很多年
I think it's silly to lie about your age.
我觉得对于岁数撒谎很蠢
- You have no redeeming vices.- I hope not.
- 你没有补偿的恶习- 我希望没有
Happy Birthday.
生日快乐
The invitation said no gifts.
邀请信上写了不要礼物
That's why I brought it now.
所以我现在把它带来了
It's too expensive. I know youdon't mean anything by it, but...
这太贵了，我知道你没什么意思...
it wouldn't look right.
但看上去不对
Gold looks right with everything.Just wear it. No-one has to know.
金子衬什么都行，戴上就是了不需要人知道
I'd know.
我知道
I do mean something by it.
我可意味深长
- Please...- It's a gift of friendship, Maggie.
- 拜托...- 这是友谊的礼物, Maggie
You'll hurt me deeply if you refuse.
如果你拒绝就太伤我了
Now look what you've made me do.
看看你现在逼的我
A little sincerity can be a verydangerous thing.
一点真诚会成为很危险的事
Any more could be fatal.
再来点就致命了
Just take the damn thing beforeI die and ruin your terrace.
在我死在你露台上前赶紧把这该死的玩艺接过去吧
It's very pretty. Thank you.
很美，谢谢你
Where's Robert? Off sendinganother telegram?
Robert在哪? 又发电报去了吗？
Signora, the florist is waitingfor his money.
女主人，花匠在等着拿工钱
I'll have to get it fromMr Windemere.
我得跟Windemere先生拿
Can he come back later?
他能呆会儿再来吗?
Has Robert a cheque-bookin his office?
Robert 在办公室不是有支票本吗？
- Can you sign on the account?- Ah, yes, of course.
- 你能在账户签单吗?- 啊，是的，当然
Tell him to wait.I'll see you tonight.
让他等一下我们今晚见了
People don't always behavethe way we expect.
人们并不总象我们希望的那样守规矩
Just the opposite. The truth is Idon't want to see you hurt.
其实正相反，事实是我不希望看到你受伤
What are you talking about?
你说什么呢?
You may need a friendone of these days.
这些日子你或许需要个朋友
When you do, I'm here.Will you remember that?
当你需要的时候，我在这里你会记得吗?
Yes, of course.
是，当然
I came as quickly as I could.
我尽快赶来了
We're all so distressed over it.
我们都很悲伤
But you mustn't take it personally.
可你不该太责备自己了
Mrs Erlynne is one ofthose women...
Erlynne太太是那种...
that attract men like abee to a flame.
火焰吸引蜜蜂一样吸引男人的女人
- A moth.- Bee to a moth.
- 是飞蛾- 飞蛾吸引蜜蜂
There must be someother explanation.
一定有其他解释
I have an idea - shallwe go for a walk?
我有个主意－咱们去散步好吗?
When there's marriage without love,there'll be love without marriage.
当婚姻没有爱时会有无婚姻的爱
But Robert and I marriedfor love...
但Robert和我是因爱而结合的...
Of course. And so did I.
当然，我也曾是的
But before the year was over...
但当热情逝去后...
Benito was lifting all kindsof petticoats.
Benito开始摆弄各式衬裙
I had to dismiss my best maid.
我不得已辞去了最好的女佣
No, no, I remember.
不，我想起来了
I passed her on tomy cousin.
我把她送给了我的表亲
Her husband was soshort-sighted, I thought.
她丈夫很短视，我觉得
But he navigated by scent,it seems.
他好像是循着气味查的
So unfortunate.
真不幸
Believe me, darling,it happens to us all.
相信我，这我们都经历过
Undying love is like theghost in your villa.
不死的爱就象你别墅里的鬼魂
Everybody talks about it...
人们都谈论...
but try and find one personwho has seen it.
但试试去找一个得到的人吧
- Can I ask you a favour?- Anything at all.
- 你能帮我个忙吗?- 任何事
About, Mrs Erlynne...
关于Erlynne太太...
Very clever woman.
很聪明的女人
She threw me out last night.
她昨晚把我扔出来了
Knows what a fool I am.Knows it as well as I do myself.
知道了我有多蠢知道的跟我自己一样清楚
She's meeting me herefor tea, though.
她会在这跟我碰面喝茶
It's a great thing to come across awoman who thoroughly understands me.
能跟一个完全理解我的女人走到一起真是太棒了
Would you mind not bringingher to our party tonight?
今晚别带她到我们的舞会你会介意吗?
That's the favour?
这是你要的帮忙吗?
Meg feels it might makethings awkward.
Meg 觉得那样会使事情变的不舒服
So it's true, then?
那么是真的喽?
I don't believe it.You don't seem the type.
我不相信，你不是那个类型
Though I will say Mrs Erlynne's damnfascinating. Hard to resist, but...
尽管我会说Erlynne太太实在迷人难以抗拒，但是……
You're not serious, are you?
你不是认真的，对吧?
I warn you, you'll have tofight me for her.
我警告你，你得跟我决斗才能抢她
And I'm a man in love.
而我可是个坠入爱河的男人
What are you talking about?
你说什么呢?
This ways, Mrs Erlynne.
这边请，Erlynne太太
- Thanks.- You're welcome.
- 多谢- 不客气
- Come with me.- Where are you taking me?
- 跟我来- 你往哪里带我?
- Let go of my arm.- I have to talk to you.
- 放开我的手- 我非跟你谈谈不可
I'm meeting Lord Augustos.
我要见Augustos大人
You must leave Amalfi at once.
你马上得离开Amalfi
And go where? You've paid myrent here for the season.
去哪?你已经替我付了一个季的租金
I'll pay it somewhere else. I wantyou on the first plane out tomorrow.
我会付其他地方的帐我要你上明天第一班飞机
- I don't understand.- People are talking.
- 我不理解- 人们在谈论
About us.
我们
I don't see the humour.
我不觉得可笑
Bury a real secret anda false one pops up in its place?
在这里，埋葬一个秘密会冒出另一个假的吗？
There's a certain irony,you have to admit.
你得承认确实这么荒谬
I'm not ready to leave.I'm enjoying myself here.
我不想走，在这挺高兴的
I'm begging you.
我恳求你
Think of Meg. If she knew thatyou were her mother...
想想Meg，如果她知道你是她妈妈...
it would destroy her.
那会毁灭她的
Meg, of the magnificentWindemeres?
Meg, 高尚的Windemeres?
Family scandal is unhealthyfor aspiring politicians.
家族丑闻对一个有抱负的政治家是不健康的
I'm not the only pragmatistin this room.
我不是这屋里唯一一个爱管闲事的人
Pragmatist? Twenty years,and not a word.
爱管闲事? 20年，音讯全无
You turn up when she marriesa man with money.
当她嫁入豪门时你倒出现了
You call that pragmatism?I can think of other words.
你管那叫爱管闲事？我有更好的形容方法
Are you trying to hurtmy feelings?
你想伤害我的感情吗?
Do you have any? That can'tbe purchased, I mean.
你有感情吗？那是不能买卖的
How much - to get youon the first flight out?
多少钱，能让你坐上头班机走开?
I feel every time he'skissed me it's filthy.
我觉得每次他吻我都是不洁的
A lie, every minute we'vebeen together.
我们在一起的每分钟都是谎言
How could he?
他怎么能呢?
Every man is born truthfuland every man dies a liar.
每个男人生来都说实话但死时都是骗子
Now, whatever you do, youmustn't make a scene.
现在，无论你做什么都不能引人注目
It's too unpleasant.And you waste your energy.
太令人不快而且也浪费你的精力
No, of course not. I wouldn't.
当然不会
Crying is the refugeof plain women.
哭是平庸女人的庇护所
Pretty women go shopping.
漂亮女人去购物
Be on that plane.I'll send the cash.
上那班飞机我会把现金奉上
Did I hear you correctly?
我没听错吧?
That Meg Windemere isyour daughter?
Meg Windemere 是你的女儿?
My daughter?
我女儿?
Robert's wife?
Robert的妻子?
How dare you.
你怎么敢
She must be twenty at least.Her mother?
她至少有20岁了，她的妈妈?
Do I look as old as all that?
我真的看上去有那么老吗?
Of course not.
当然不是
I must have nodded off.
我一定是在打盹
You were dozing.Go back to sleep.
你困了，回去接着睡吧
Come on.
快点
No business tonight.We can talk another day.
今晚不谈生意，我们改天再谈
- Good to see you.- Lovely party.
-高兴见到你-晚会真好
More champagne.
再来点香槟
Welcome.Have a great party.
欢迎，好好玩
- Good evening, Mr Dumby.- Oh, good evening, Mrs Stutfield.
- 晚上好，Dumby先生- 哦，晚上好，Stutfield太太
Last party of the season,I suppose.
这一季最后的晚会了吧
- It's been delightful, hasn't it?- Quite delightful.
- 真令人愉快，是吧?- 非常令人愉快
Good evening. Here it is,the last party of the season.
晚上好，这里，是本季最后的晚会了
I suppose so. It's been a very dullseason, though, hasn't it?
我猜也是，尽管是个闷人的季节是吧？
Dull. Yes, terribly dull.
闷人，是啊，很闷
- Evening, Cecil.- Hello, Dumby.
－晚安, Cecil- 你好, Dumby
I suppose this'll be the lastparty of the season.
我希望这是本季最后的晚会了
Surely not. Probablybe two more at least.
肯定不是，至少还会有两个
I had the oddest dream today.
我今天做了个怪透了的梦
A bit of it has justcome back to me...
刚刚想起了一小部分...
So what are we drinking?
我们喝什么呢?
- Where's the birthday girl?- Transforming herself.
- 生日女郎在哪里?- 正在变形
Sausages and women.
香肠和女人
If you want to enjoy theexperience...
如果你想享受她们...
never watch thepreparation of either.
千万别看过程
- Is that new?- Just out of the box. Do you like it?
- 那是新的吗?- 刚出盒，你喜欢吗?
You might be a little cold.I'll get you a wrap.
你会有点冷，我给你拿个披肩吧
And spoil the lines? Didn't your friendteach you about Italian fashion?
毁掉线条吗，你朋友没教你意大利时装吗?
My friend?
我朋友?
I saw the cheques. Don't even...
我看见支票了，少来...
Lady Plymdale, so good ofyou to come.
Plymdale女士, 你来真好
Do you want another glass ofchampagne?
再要一杯香槟吗?
Let's get us both some.
我俩都来点吧
Why don't you ask me how I am?
你怎么给我问安?
I like people to ask.
我喜欢人给我问安
It shows a widespreadinterest in my health.
表示对我健康的普遍关心
And you can't imagine howcomforting that is.
你不会知道那让人多舒服
Lovely party.
晚会不错
- How are you, Cecil?- Oh, not well at all.
- 你好, Cecil?- 一点都不好
I'd like Alessandra...
我希望Alessandra...
to know Mr. Hopperfrom Australia.
认识一下从澳洲来的Hopper先生
- Would you introduce her?- Would you just excuse me for a moment?
- 你可以介绍一下吗?- 请容我一点时间好吗?
Go with Mr Windemere.Thank you.
跟Windemere先生走谢谢
She's my last, you know.I will miss her.
她是我最小的，我会想她的
But it's best to get them outof the nest...
但是在她们开始攻击你之前...
before they turn on you.
还是把她们从巢里赶走吧
Girls begin by loving their mothers.But as they grow they judge us.
女孩最初是爱妈妈的但长大后就会评价你
Rarely do they forgive us.
很少会宽容
Oh, poor fool.He'll never learn.
哦，可怜的傻子就是学不会
Which fool?Don't make me choose.
那个傻子？别让我选
Tuppy,he's brought Mrs Erlynne.
Tuppy,他把Erlynne太太带来了
All the women will snub her.
所有女人都会怠慢她
She may have betterluck with the men.
她跟男人在一起没准会有点运气
It is because of men...
那是因为男人...
that women distrust other women.
女人才不信任女人
Women don't trust women,men don't trust women...
女人不信女人,男人也不信女人...
no-one trusts women.
没人相信女人
It's what binds the Hinduand the Catholic.
就是这个联合了印度教和天主教
I know I promised, but I must tellyou how beautiful you look tonight.
我知道我发过誓但我必需说你今晚真美
Well, if you must, you must.
好吧，如果你非说就说吧
I beg your pardon, I waslooking for someone else.
请原谅，我在找其他人
Well, you found me.
而你找到了我
Mrs Erlynne.
Erlynne太太
May I call you Stella?
我可以叫你Stella吗？
Lord Augustus is gettingme champagne.
Augustus大人给我拿香槟去了
You and I can trade favours.
你和我可以交换恩宠
Tempting, but no.
很诱人，但算了
I'd rather he didn't see us under themoonlight. He might misunderstand.
我宁愿他不会看到月光下的我们或许会令他误解
Hear me out.
听我说
Windemere's fortune exceeds Tuppy's.
Windemere财富胜过Tuppy
Why change horses now?
干嘛现在换马?
You can have waht youwant and Meg's free.
你得到所要的，Meg也自由了
Free?
自由?
She hasn't the courage to leave him.
她没有离开他的勇气
But if it's clear to her thathe's with you...
但如果明确了他跟你在一起...
He's not.
他没有
You've been buying idle gossip.You should get a refund.
你买的谣言不可靠，赶紧去退款吧
Excuse me.
请原谅
I had to invite her, Dumby.
我非邀请她不可, Dumby
The point is, she's a changed woman.You can see it in her eyes.
问题是，她变了你可以从她眼睛里看出来
Do you think she'd look atyou if you were poor?
你以为你要是穷她会看你一眼吗?
Do you think I'd look at herif she were ugly?
那你以为如果她丑我会看她吗?
Fair's fair, exchange ratesand so forth.
公平是公平，互利互惠
I know she's had her thisand her that, but...
我知道她有点这有点那...
if a man can toleratehis own past...
但如果男人能有过去...
Why not a past in his wife?At any rate...
他妻子干嘛不能有?而且肯出钱...
it's wipe the slate.Clean start.
什么都能擦干净重新开始
She and I, we...understand each other.
她和我……我们可以互相理解
And you know what they say.
你知道他们怎么说
Every saint has past,every sinner has a future.
每个圣人都有个过去而每个罪人都有个未来
I'm going to ask her to marryme if she'll have me.
如果她肯要，我想向她求婚
You know why they call itan altar, Tuppy?
你知道人们为什么称之为圣坛, Tuppy?
It's where they makehuman sacrifices.
因为那里以人为祭祀
I had a dream aboutMrs Erlynne today.
我今天梦到 Erlynne太太
Yes, well...
是吗...
you couldn't help it,I suppose. She...
你是情不自禁吧...
she is quite the woman.
她真了不起
But in future...
但以后……
please try to dream ofsomeone else.
还是请梦别人去吧
Don't you think you'vehad enough?
你不觉得自己喝够了吗?
- Lovely party.- Thanks for coming.
- 晚会很好- 谢谢赏光
Meg?
I have to change.
我得去换衣服
- Did you see her?- Don't.
- 你看见她了吗?- 没有
You're lovely.
你很可爱
It's ridiculous on a woman at her age.
她那岁数的女人穿真荒唐
Why didn't you tell me?
你干嘛不告诉我?
You said you were my friend.
你说过你是我的朋友
Men and women can't be friends.
男女之间无法成朋友
- Meg?- No.
- Meg?- 不
Can you stay with him?
你能跟他在一起吗?
Can you get into bedwith him tonight?
你今晚能跟他上床吗?
Tomorrow night?Nights after that?
明晚?以后呢？
You said yourself, there's noforgiving a man who betrays his wife.
你自己说的，男人背叛妻子不可原谅
What will you choose?
你怎么选?
A false degrading marriage, or yourown true self, free of compromise?
一个虚伪可耻的婚姻还是一个没有妥协的真我？
I've loved you from the beginning.It's the truth.
我对你一见钟情，这是真的
Moment you held out your hand to me inthe glove shop, I thought 'there she is".
你在手套店抽出手来的那刻我想“就是她了”
And then, suppose I'd walkedby without stopping?
那时，我是否该不加停留的离去呢?
Just the thought of it.
只那样一想
I've never loved anyone until now.
至今我从未爱过
Stop.
停
John?
I'm sorry, I didn't meanto startle you.
对不起，我不想吓你
I'm looking for Meg. If you see her,it's important.
我在找Meg，你看见她了吗？
Have you had a row?
你排队了吗?
A little misunderstanding.
一个小舞会
Try the bar.
看看酒吧
Tuppy's given up smokes for her.
Tuppy为她戒烟了
Women.
女人
Women inspire us to great things.
Women 给我们向上的灵感
Then somehow prevent usfrom doing any of them.
却又不明所以地阻止我们实施
He's proposing to her.
他向她求婚了
It will be his third time up the aisle.
该是他第三次上圣坛了
Hope trumps experience, Dumby.
希望是个制胜之举， Dumby
It's God's joke on the human race.
是人类竞争中上帝之玩笑而已
He's quite convinced she'schanged her spots.
他确信她已改过自新了
Care to make it interesting?
想把那变有趣吗?
I told you I was serious.
告诉你我是认真的了
Hasn't anyone warned youagainst me?
没有人警告你该反对我吗?
Oh, yes. Everyone.
哦，是的，所有人
Put it away.
把它拿开
Now, you don't have to loveme right away.
你并不用马上就爱上我
Think of the money.
想想钱
Suppose I marry you, and in a yearyour investments go sour.
假设我跟你结婚一年内你的投资缩水了
I'll be stuck with a pauper.
我就被个叫花子栓住了
On the other hand...
另一个情形是...
I could drop dead on the golf coursenext Tuesday...
我可能下礼拜二死在高尔夫球场……
and you'd be left verywell-appointed.
而你可就富裕了
Life's a gamble, Stella.
生命就是赌博, Stella
I don't know what to say.
我不知如何作答
People say too much as it is.
人讲太多话
Mrs Windemere andMrs Erlynne...
Windemere太太跟Erlynne太太...
Iook like mother and daughter,don't they?
看起来就跟母女是的，是吧?
They're wearing the same dress.
他们穿着同样的衣服
Well, that'll be it.
就是的
Come away with me.
跟我走吧
We could set sail tonight.
我们今晚就出海
Please.
求你
Is this your idea of a joke?
这是你开玩笑的方式吗？
I need to speak to you.It's about Darlington.
我得跟你谈谈Darlington
Follow me.
跟我来
He's in love with Meg.
他爱上Meg了
I know we said cash, so I'm raisingthe amount. I want you to leave now.
我知道我说到钱的问题，我要提高数目让你现在就走
I'd be more concernedif I were you.
我要是你会更小心的
You're not me.
你不是我
The problem is I've beenlying to my wife...
问题是我对我妻子说谎了...
and I'm not very good at it.
而我很不在行
I can add up the rumours...
我可以再添加谣言...
and show her a big fat zero.I'm Tuppy's girl.
让她看什么都没有我是Tuppy的女人
- Case closed.- I'll do my own explaining, get out.
- 案件结束了- 我自己会解释，你出去吧
I'd like to say goodbye to her.
我要跟她道别
You said goodbye to her twentyyears ago. No second chances.
你20年前就跟她道别了没有选择余地
I'll leave first.
我先离开
- We shouldn't walk out together.- You're the expert.
- 我们不该一起出去- 你是专家
Count to a 100.
数100下
Mrs Windemere?
Windemere太太?
Dear Robert, I thought ourmarriage was perfect.
亲爱的Robert, 我以为我们的婚姻是完美的
I thought we wouldalways be together.
我以为我们永远会在一起
If you love Mrs Erlynne,you should be with her.
如果你爱Erlynne太太,你该跟他在一起
I feel so foolish.
我觉得真愚蠢
Everyone knew but me.
每个人都知道，只有我不知道
Meg, let me in,I wanna talk to you.
Meg, 让我进去我要跟你谈谈
Please, open the door.
请开门
There is nothing between meand Stella Erlynne.
我和Stella Erlynne之间什么都没有
How can you think it?
你怎么能那么想?
She's old for God's sake.She dyes her hair.
上帝她那么老，还染头发
She paints her facelike an Indian.
她象印度人一样粉刷她的脸
She's a cold,selfish woman.
她是个冷血自私的女人
Not all attractiveonce you know her.
如果你认识她就知道她根本不吸引人
Look, she was goingto damage someone.
她想毁灭一个人
A person who'd never doneher any harm.
一个不会伤害她的人
She came here with a secret thatwould have broken your heart.
她带来的秘密会伤你的心
Look, I wanted to tell you. I justdidn't know how.
我想告诉你，但不知如何做
I was trying to protect you,you have to believe me.
我是想保护你，你得相信我
She asked me for moneyand I gave it to her, but...
她管我要钱，我给了她...
I'm not proud ofbeing blackmailed...
我并不以被勒索而自豪...
I didn't know what else to do.
我不知所措
I should have told youat the start.
我该开始就告诉你的
I'm not lying to you now, I...
我不打算再骗你了...
I love you.
我爱你
And there's no otherwoman in my heart...
我心里没有别人...
or in my bed.
床上也没有
Meg...
please open the door.
请开门
We both had toomuch champagne.
我俩都喝太多香槟了
We can talk in the morning.
我们明早再谈吧
- Splendid.- Thank you for coming.
- 太棒了- 谢谢你来
- Lovely party. Goodnight, Robert.- I'll see you at the club.
- 晚会不错， Robert.- 我们在俱乐部见
- There's the girl.- Take Windemere to the club.
- 女孩在这里啊-带Windemere去俱乐部
Keep him out all night.Get him drunk if you have to.
整晚守着他，如果能就灌醉他
- Just don't let him come home.- Why?
- 就是别让他回家- 为什么?
What? What?
什么啊？
I like you, I do.
我喜欢你，真的
But if this is going to workbetween us, you can't do that.
但是如果想奏效的话，你就不能那样
- Do what?- "Where? What? Why?"
- 哪样？- “哪里？什么？为什么”
I can't always explainmyself to myself...
我不能老解释跟...
let alone anyone else.
别人解释自己
Good for you -takes the pressure off.
不错，放开压力
Nine times out of ten, mendon't give two pins about why...
9成的男人...
they just feel obligedto take an interest.
无法接受被强加的兴趣
So, I'll do exactly as you wish...
那么我就按吩咐行事...
and I'll feel as ifwe're married already.
假装感觉我们已经结婚了
Oh, can you get yourselfhome all right?
哦，你能安全回家吗?
Why, Tuppy...
哇, Tuppy...
you're the first man who'sasked me that.
你是第一个这么问我的男人
I don't need to be the first,Stella. Just the last.
我不必是第一个Stella，就当最后一个吧
There's a taxi waitingat the end of the dock.
在码头上有辆出租车等着
My husband sent you.
我丈夫让你来的
Your husband thinks you'rein bed sleeping off...
你丈夫以为你喝了一瓶矿泉水...
a litre of Perrier Jouet.
已经睡了
Let's go.
走吧
He gave me money,that's all.
他给我钱了，就这样
I'm an old friend of the family.
我是家族的老朋友
Do you think I'm stupid?
你以为我傻吗?
Married to man you loveand running off...
嫁给了一个爱的人，又跟...
with an international playboy?Do I think you're stupid?
一个国际花花公子离家?我以为你傻?
This is none of your business.
这跟你无关
You think because hems are higherand women can vote...
你以为开衩变高了，我们可以投票...
that anything hasreally changed for us?
一切就会为我们而改变吗?
Friends will stop calling.
朋友们会不跟你联系
He'll be invited into homesyou're not.
他会受邀回家，而你不会
You manage.
你可以做到
Don't compare yourself.
别吓比较
It takes practice andskill to live without regret.
无悔的生活需要准备和练习
A marriage takesyour whole heart.
一段婚姻需要你整个心灵
Selfish people can't pull it off,but you're not that.
自私的人做不到，但你不是
You can succeed wherethe rest of us fail.
我们都失败了你也不会
- Why should I believe you?- Don't believe me, believe him.
- 我干嘛要信你?- 别信我，信他
He's been faithful to you,I'll swear it on my life.
他对你是忠诚的，我以性命担保
He told you to lie.
他让你撒谎
He doesn't evenknow you're here.
他甚至不知道你在这
He never has to know.
他不必知道
You want me to lie again?
你让我再撒谎吗?
Everything's spoiledbetween us. I can't.
我们间的一切都完了，我不能
What's happened to you?
你怎么了?
Who taught you to be sounforgiving?
谁教你这么不能宽容?
You made a mistake,don't make it worse.
你犯了个错，别再犯了
You shut your eyes to everythingthat isn't perfect...
你对不完美的东西熟视无睹...
you're just asking to fallinto a hole.
你被带向一个陷阱
Fine.
好吧
Go ahead.
去吧
Step over love to pick uppride and guilt.
放弃爱而选择傲慢和内疚吧
What will that tradebe worth in a year?
真是20岁这一年里
In twenty?
最赔了买卖了
Darlington, does your boatreally have to be so big?
Darlington, 你的船非得这么大吗?
You know what they say aboutmen with big boats.
你知道人们怎么议论有大船的男人吗？
- I should be getting home.- You'll take a cigar, surely?
- 我得回家了- 你得抽支雪茄，真的?
I thought you'd quitfor the love of a good woman.
我以为你放弃对好女人的爱了呢
Good woman isn't exactly themoniker I'd choose for Mrs Erlynne.
好女人可不是 Erlynne太太的名字
You imply she'sthe devil's handmaiden.
你在暗示她是魔鬼的侍女吗？
Dumby and I are just concernedfor your future.
Dumby和我正为你的未来担忧呢
Devilish women are a bother,and good ones are a bore.
魔鬼般的女人是麻烦好女人又太闷了
That's the only difference.
那是唯一的不同
Mrs Erlynne is neither a bothernor a bore.
Erlynne太太即不是麻烦也不是沉闷
You change your habits,but I doubt she'll change hers.
你改变了习惯但我怀疑她也会改变
I've bet Dumby fifty quid.
我跟 Dumby 赌了50块
Enough of this.
够了
I won't hear any more wordssaid against her.
我不想听反对她的话了
She's everything I've everwanted in a woman.
她是我对女人一切愿望的完美体现
My dear Tuppy, in this worldthere are only two tragedies.
我亲爱的Tuppy,这世界上只有两个惨剧
One is not getting what one wants,the other is getting it.
一是一无所获，一是得偿所愿
The last is very much the worst.The last is a real tragedy.
后者是最差的，真正的惨剧
Marriage.
婚姻
It has its pains - ask Edna.
痛苦万分，问Edna
Celibacy has no pleasures.
单身生活没乐趣
- What would you know about it?- I can learn.
- 你怎么知道?- 我可以学
If it will prove my love.
来证明我的爱
A woman who needs proof?
女人需要验证?
Before she'll leave her husband.
在她离开她丈夫以前
John, you are a cad.
John,你是个无赖
We're all in the gutter.
我们都在臭水沟里
But some of us are looking at the stars.
而我们中的一些人却在看星星
What men call gallantry...
男人称它为“殷勤”
ans God's adultery...
上帝称它为“通奸”
is far more common where the climate's sultry.
这种事在天气闷热的地方，尤其容易发生
That's the one I bought Meg.
那是我买给Meg的
For her birthday.
生日礼物
Are you sure?
你肯定吗?
She must have left it last weekwhen you came for lunch.
必是上次你来吃饭时她落在这的
She was carrying it tonight.
可她今晚拿着来着
One fan looks very muchlike another.
扇子彼此相象
John?
- I've no idea.- Meg's not here, is she?
- 我不知道- Meg不是在这里吧?
No, of course not.
当然不是
- What's that?- I didn't hear anything.
- 那是什么?- 我什么都没听见
She's downstairs.
她在楼下
Calm down.You've had too much...
冷静你喝太多了...
Don't make an ass of yourself.
别让你自己出丑
Too late.
太晚了
- Bloody hell!- You better put some ice on that.
- 该死- 你弄点冰敷上吧
I thought it was mine.
我以为是我的呢
I must have picked upMrs Windemere's by mistake.
肯定是误拿了Windemere的
Tuppy, I swear, I had no idea.
Tuppy, 我发誓，我不知道
You owe Cecil fifty quid. Sorry.
你欠Cecil 50磅，对不起
It seems I'm the ass,Windemere. Not you.
好像是我出丑了Windemere，不是你
I spent the night on John's boat.
我在John船上过的夜
I had too much to drink.
我喝多了
Can I ask you to forgive me?
你能原谅我吗?
I did something very stupidlast night.
我昨夜做了很蠢的事
You're not in my league.
你不是我的同伙
I made a complete ass of myself.
我出了大丑
Ruined it for poor Tuppy.
毁了Tuppy
Better now than later, I guess.
但我想这迟早会发生
Tuppy?
His engagement toMrs Erlynne is off.
他取消了向Erlynne太太求婚
What are you talking about?
你说什么呢?
Last night on John's yacht, MrsErlynne was waiting in his bedroom.
昨晚在John游艇上，Erlynne在他卧室里等他
Look, I was drunk, I thought...
看，我喝多了，我以为...
I saw your fan, I thought that...
我看见了你的扇子，我以为...
I didn't think.
我没用脑子
It was her.
是她
She said she took it by mistake.
她说是她误拿了
- No, that's not true.- Oh, of course not.
- 不，那不是事实- 当然不是
Better count the spoons.
最好数数勺子
You were rightnot to want her here.
你不让她来是对的
I'd have expected more from John,though. Tuppy's his friend.
我对John期望挺高的，Tuppy可是他的朋友啊
She didn't take my fan.I left it on the...
她没拿我的扇子，我把它...
There's a telephone callfrom America.
有美国的电话
It's your father, Mr Windemere.
是你父亲，Windemere 先生
Not now.
现在不行
No, I'll take it.He'll worry.
我来接，他会担心的
- I love you.- I love you.
- 我爱你- 我爱你
And a woman brought this.
一个女人送来这个
She's waiting downstairs.
她在楼下等
Thank you.
谢谢
What are you doing here?We had an agreement.
你在这里干嘛?我们有协议
I came to return the fan.
我回来还扇子
How is your wifefeeling this morning?
你太太今早怎么样?
You don't get within ten feetof my wife.
你不许靠近我太太10尺
I only asked how she was.
我只是问候她
If you're here to tellher who you are...
如果你来这告诉她你是谁...
it's better coming from me.
还是我来吧
It's my secret, not yours.
是我的秘密，不是你的
You've kept it very well.
你保守的很好
Twenty years is a long time.
20年是个很久的时间
It doesn't seem to have beentoo much of a strain.
没造成什么伤害
You see a little girl...
你看个小女孩...
the right age,you push the thought aside.
合适的岁数把想法放在一边
Close the door.
关上门
Only at three o'clock,that in-between hour...
只在三点……
too late to do anything,too early for dinner...
干什么都晚了，吃饭有太早...
doors come flying open.
门大敞着
I don't believe you feelanything for her.
我不觉得你对她有感情
You care about yourself,and no-one else.
你只顾自己，没别人
Robert.
Your father needs to talk to you,he says it's important.
你父亲要跟你说话，很重要
Mrs Erlynnecame to return your fan.
Erlynne太太来还你扇子
She was just leaving.
她刚要走
No, don't leave, I need tospeak with you.
不，别走，我要跟你说话
- She'll miss her plane.- Just a few minutes.
- 她会耽误航班- 就一会儿
Your father's waiting on the phone.He said it's important.
你父亲在等你接电话，说是重要事
It would be a great mistake...
误航班...
to miss your plane.
会是个大错
I came to make sureyou got home safely.
我来确认你安全到家了
You can't leave yet.
你还不能走
You're my only witness thatnothing happened.
你是证明没事发生的唯一证人
Your witness?
你的证人?
I'm going to tell him the truth.
我要告诉他真相
What you did is your mistake.
你做错了
Your sack of bricks. You carry it.
你的麻烦，你来扛吧
You don't confess and had it offto someone who loves you.
你不能忏悔后把痛苦留给爱你的人
But everybody thinksyou were having...
但所有人都觉得你...
They'll think it anyway.It doesn't matter.
他们反正要那么想，没关系
That's not true,it matters to Tuppy.
那不是真相，对Tuppy来说有关系
I can't be responsiblefor ruining that.
我无法对毁了你们的婚约熟视无睹
You wanna spoil the onegood thing I've ever done?
你想把我做过的唯一善举给毁了吗?
It's only right to tell himthe truth.
告诉他真相是对的
You love each other!That's your truth.
你们相爱，这就是事实
Why you giving up your chanceof marriage to save mine?
你干嘛放弃一段好婚姻而拯救我?
- It doesn't make any sense.- I'll tell you the truth.
- 没道理- 我告诉你真相
But first, promise you're notgoing to make...
但首先答应我...
some grand confession.
不会去做大忏悔
Swear it on whatever youhold sacred.
以圣名起誓
I swear on my mother.
我以我母亲起誓
Pardon?
什么?
She's my guardian angel.
她是我的守护天使
My whole life, I've wantedto be like her.
我的一生，都想象她那样
I'm sure she wouldn't hold youto such a standard.
我确信她不想你以她为标准
She'd be so ashamed of me now.
她此时一定以我为耻
We all straddle the abyss,Mrs Windemere.
我们都在深渊挣扎，Windemere太太
If we never look down, how canwe know who we are?
如果我们不下望又怎能知道自己的真相?
A mother could never be ashamedof a daughter who didn't fall in.
母亲永远也不会因不堕落的女儿为耻
I hope you're right.
我希望你对
I've never been more certainof anything.
我从未如此确信过
I swear, them.
我发誓
What is it you wanted to tell me?
你要告诉我什么?
Nothing.
没事
I'll miss my plane.
我要耽误航班了
Goodbye, Mrs Windemere.
再见， Windemere太太
I hope we meet again.
我希望我们再见
So do I.
我也是
Mrs Erlynne.
Erlynne太太
- You didn't tell her?- No.
- 你没告诉她吧?- 没有
Why not?
为什么?
She has a mother.
她有母亲
A photograph in a locket.
小盒里的照片
It's a fairy tale.
那是个神话
A kind, caring mother, who lovesand watches over her.
一个善良、温存的妈妈，爱她，照顾她
I'm not going to take that away.
我不能把那个带走
And neither should you.
你也不该
Mrs Erlynne,One thousand Dollars.
Erlynne太太,1000美元
For one night I thought you were inlove with another woman.
有一晚，我觉得你爱上了其他女人
For one night I thought you were inlove with another man.
有一晚我以为你爱上了其他男人
- She was right.- Who?
- 她是对的- 谁?
Mrs Erlynne said we can'tshut our eyes...
Erlynne太太说我们不该对...
to everything that isn't perfect...
不完美熟视无睹...
otherwise we might fallinto a huge abyss.
否则我们会坠入深渊
We almost fell.
我们差一点
She's a smart woman.
她是个聪明的女人
She's a good woman.
她是个好女人
Better than I thought.
比我想的好
She insisted.
她很坚持
Who?
谁?
Meg.Something to remember her by.
Meg，一个对她的念想
And she explained everything.
而且她解释了一切
Everything?
一切?
Oh, yes, couse.The flat tyre, the dog.
哦，对，当然瘪轮胎，狗
The Brazilian taxi diver with thepregnant daughter...
巴西出租车司机和怀孕的女儿……
who lost her purse.
丢了钱包
And the only thing I can sayin my defense is...
而我的辩解是...
that I have no defense.
我没什么可辩解的
I jumped to conclusions andthought the worst.
我跳到结论，直接往最坏想
Where's this old crate going to?
这破筐往哪去?
I don't know.
我不知道
Will you marry me when get there?
到地方后你会嫁给我吗?
A man gets the wife he deserves.
男人娶该娶的女人为妻
Well, I've been a very, very bad man.
而我，可是一个很坏很坏的男人
You know, John,love's a battleground.
你知道，John,爱是战场
It was only a flesh wound.
而那只是皮肉之伤
Men advance,women resist.
男人预支，女人隐忍
We retreat and theyblock our escape.
我们退缩他们就堵住我们的退路
We can't win.
我们不能赢的
The sexes will never understandeach other.
两性无法彼此理解
Only because they take such painsto deceive each other.
他们以伤彼此伤害
Oh, hello Dumby,are you awake?
哦，Dumby,你醒着吗?
Am I winning?
我赢了吗?